

An Airline Customer Service Agent with four years of experience specializing in communication, client relations, operational support, and process improvement. Adept at interfacing with a diverse range of passengers to identify solutions and ensure customer satisfaction.

Professional Experience

Airline Customer Service Agent

Frontier Airlines, San Francisco, CA | September 2019 - Present

- Build relationships with customers, utilizing de-escalation techniques to resolve passenger issues calmly and professionally, and maintain a 93% customer satisfaction rating
- Identify solutions to boarding issues and complications, field inquiries from passengers, and provide hotel and meal accommodations due to flight delaysand cancellations
- Coo rd i n ate with ai rport staff to m a nage baggage serv ices, ti ckets, andboarding procedures while ensuring compliance with safety regulations

Airline Customer Service Agent

JetBlue Airlines, San Francisco, CA | May 2018 - September 2019

- Coordinated with airline customer service agents in a collaborative team environment and provided support to colleagues to resolve customer challenges and issues
- Performed account lookups, verified travel documentation, and provided information to travelers to ensure safe boarding and proper accommodations

123 Santa Maria, San Francisco, CA 12345 selen ara m i rez@exa m p le.co m (123) 456-7890

Education

Bachelor of Arts (BA) Communication University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA Septem be r 2015 - May 2019

Key Skills

- ◆ Airline Customer Service
- * Avi at io n Secu rity
- * Board i ng Proced u res
- ♦ Team Collaboration
- Safety Regulations